Elmina R. Lucke Papers, 1897-1987
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- Series IV. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIALS AND MEMORABILIA
  - Memorabilia
    - German language study, Berlin: notebooks, 1913 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Invitations, 1930-75, undated (Box 4, Folder 15-17)
    - Mementoes of trip: note, map, printed material, miscellaneous items, 1930-31 (Box 4, Folder 18-19)
    - Passports, 1925-59 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Gentle on My Mind by Louise Gates Eddy: book and clippings, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous, 1926-81, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Series V. PHOTOGRAPHS
  - Around-the-world trip, 1930-31 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Elmina R. Lucke, 1912?-1986 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Family, 1897?-1986, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Friends, 1920s, 1948-84 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - India, 1947-85 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - PPSEAWA Seventh Annual Conference, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - University of Michigan, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Albums
    - Burma and India, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - India, 1946-49 (Box 5)